<resources>
    <string name="app_name">H2k-price-comparer</string>
    <string name="title_activity_admin">Admin</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="samsung_s8">Latest flagship by Samsung made its place on top just because of its quality and uniqueness. Although it is one of the expensive smartphones in Pakistan right now. But without any doubt, we can say Galaxy S8 is really rich in its specifications and features like its price. The giant, Samsung S8 features everything, which a smartphone user can desire. Because of its Infinity edge display, powerful processor, high-end camera department and battery of 3000mAh, Galaxy S8 will never disappoint you. </string>
    <string name="iphone_7">The second best smartphone you can buy right now in Pakistan is no other than Apple’s iPhone 7 Plus. Rich cameras, uninterruptible processor, and its design are the main qualities we can tell you right now about iPhone 7 Plus. Although it’s younger sibling iPhone 7 is not that bad but iPhone 7 plus made its place on this list because of its dual camera and bigger size. What makes it different from previous iPhone 6 Plus is that it is water resistance, supports dual camera sensors and comes with 3GB of RAM. If you are an iOS lover than we will suggest you iPhone 7+ without any doubt</string>
    <string name="oppo_f3">The selfie expert Oppo F3 is the newest handset by Oppo. Right now, it is the top smartphone under the range of Rs. 30,000. It is another innovation by Oppo in smartphone’s optics. Its 16+8 mega pixels dual front camera made it selfie expert. F3 boasts powerful features like Octa-core 1.5GHz processor, 4GB of RAM and 64GB of storage. It’s super selfie dual camera will never let you down whenever you are partying with your family and friends</string>
    <string name="j5_pro">Galaxy J5 Pro is another budget smartphone by Samsung. If you really love Galaxy and your pocket don’t allow you to buy any of S or Note series smartphone then go for Galaxy J5 prowhich packs rich features and powerful hardware. It is a smart Galaxy handset with a smart price. With Super AMOLED 5.2-inches display, 1.6GHz octa-core CPU, 3GB RAM and 32GB storage, J5 pro is really a good device</string>
    <string name="Q_mobile_Z12">Z12 Pro by QMobile is another budget smartphone you can buy. It is one of the best-selling smartphones by QMobile in Pakistan. Comes in stylish metal body design and with a powerful battery. It is the cheapest smartphone in this list with high-end specifications. Phone packing 5.5 inches display, 1.3 GHz processor coupled with 3GB RAM and 32GB of internal storage. It is considerable if you want big size display with low price. </string>
    <string name="Vivo_y55s">Last, in the list Y55s comes with the display size of 5.2-inches and 3GB of RAM. Design wise look like Oppo A57. We will suggest you this smartphone if you want a smartphone with simple design but strong with body and hardware. Over all specs are good according to its price. </string>
    <string name="J5_prime">Galaxy J5 Prime packs a 5-inches HD display with Quad-core 1.4GHz processor joined with 2GB of Ram and 16GB of ROM supports microSD. The phone runs Android OS, v6.0.1 (Marshmallow). Here you will enjoy the same camera as of previous J5 2016. Phone have a battery of 2400mAh which is Non-removable Li-Ion. It was launched in October 2016.</string>
    <string name="Grand_prime">Recently the most selling smartphone by Samsung in the market features a 5-inches display. Grand Prime Plus comes with Quad-core 1.4 GHz processor along with 1.5GB of Ram and 8GB of ROM supports microSD. This phone convey 8MP Back and 5MP front camera with the battery power of 2600Ah.</string>
    <string name="Hawai_Honor_6x">5.5-inches Huawei honor 6X was introduced in October 2016. Honor 6x is powered by Octa-core processor coupled with 3GB of Ram and 32GB of ROM supports microSD. The phone runs Android OS, v6.0 (Marshmallow) carrying dual 12MP primary and 5MP front facing camera. Supports a non-removable Li-Ion 3100mAh battery.
</string>
    <string name="oppp_A57">One of the latest smartphone from Oppo in Pakistan Oppo A57 offers a 5.2-inches display along with dominant Octa-core 1.4 GHz processor. The smartphone is loaded with 3GB of Ram and 32GB of ROM and supports microSD card as well. Oppo A57 offers a 2900mAh non-removable battery.</string>
    <string name="Envy_15">The new edition to HP’s long line of ENVY family is much lighter and thinner aluminum framed body and is among the best selling laptops in Pakistan. Its new display features brighter colors. ENVY 15 is a fast gadget with Intel Core i7 processor and 16GB of RAM. The 7th generation laptop can have 1TB or 256 SSD hard drive. The new laptop is much premium than the last models with a new and improved colorful panel, discreet graphics. </string>
    <string name="Probook_450">Probook 450 G3 employs 15.6 inches Full HD screen with 1920 x 1080 pixels resolution which makes the screen look bold and bright. The device is available in both Intel Corei7 and Corei5 with 4GB RAM and is designed for professional and homemade use with 500GB internal storage. The device runs smoothly and has the least complaints in the Pakistani market.</string>
    <string name="Dell_inspiron_5559">Another addition to best selling laptops of 2016, the Inspiron 5559 has a simple look and a plastic lid with a jagged texture making it durable. The laptop has a 15.6-inch screen with a resolution of 1366 x 768. Inspiron 5559 has two models available in Pakistan having 8GB or 16GB RAM with the Intel Core i5 and i7 processor respectively. The 6th generation laptop is priced at PKR 76,000 for 8GB and PKR 95000 for 16GB RAM model.</string>
    <string name="Lenovo_ideapad_110">The everyday affordable laptop by Lenovo has a simple design. It has a 15.6” HD Glossy LED Screen with 1366 x 768 resolutions. The device is loaded with 4GB RAM and Intel Pentium processor which is enough for everyday work and surfing the internet. Ideapad 110 uses HDD hard disk with the storage up to 1TB (1000GB) which is a massive space to store digital files. In Pakistani market, this device is available in PKR 37000 with warranty.</string>
    <string name="Lenovo_ideapad_310">Another everyday use laptop by Lenovo in the series has been categorically more in demand in Pakistani market. It offers up to Up to 15.6-inch FHD screen with 920 x 1080 resolutions in various editions of this model. Ideapad 310 has Up to 6th Generation Intel Core i7 and i5 processor with the internal storage of up to 1 TB HDD or up to 256 GB SSD. The Core i5 and Core i7 are available in Pakistan with the price tag of PKR 49,000 and PKR 66,000 respectively.</string>
    <string name="Macbook_air">MacBook Air lasts up to an incredible 12 hours between charges. So from your morning coffee till your evening commute, you can work unplugged. When it’s time to kick back and relax, you can get up to 12 hours of iTunes movie playback. And with up to 30 days of standby time, you can go away for weeks and pick up right where you left off.</string>
    _
    <string name="latitude_6430">The Dell Latitude E6430 has the same attractive gunmetal gray aluminum lid, matte chrome body and angular sides as its predecessor, the Dell Latitude E6420. With a snazzy design that reminds us a sci-fi spaceship, the E6430 stands out in the world of staid black-and-gray business notebooks.</string>
    <string name="Dell_xps">The Dell XPS 13 was unveiled at CES 2012. It is the companies first Ultrabook, a term coined by Intel. The XPS 13 features a 13.3-inch screen (1366 x 768 NON Touch Corning Gorilla Glass) and uses flash memory to help with fast booting.</string>
    <string name="Lenovo_yoga_pro_3">Lenovo says they are launching the Yoga 3 Pro as a Best Buy exclusive. It packs an Intel Core M-70 processor, with a 256GB SSD, up to 8GB of RAM, and the same 3,200 × 1,800 resolution screen found in the Yoga 2 Pro.The Core M CPU helps theYoga 3 Pro achieve a claimed battery life rating of up to nine hours.</string>
    <string name="Alienware_R2"> A feast for the eyes: Enjoy a full 13.3" LCD screen that offers stunningly clear graphics anywhere. The Alienware 13 is available with your choice of brilliant HD, Full HD or choose a High Graphics Machine Which support all gamers and randering works for graphics designer </string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
</resources>
